Guide to the Consumer Reports. Advocacy records, 1927-2011 and undated RL.11780
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Statements, Comments, Testimonies, etc., 1954-2001 and undated; 3
  - 1980, 16
    - 8002003-1. Insulation, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8002004-0. Insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8002005-2. Dairy products, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8003001-1. Mortgages, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8003002-1. International trade, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8003003-1. Mortgages, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8003004-1. Federal Reserve Board, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8003005-1. Department of Commerce, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8003006-1. Department of State, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8003007-1. Telecommunications, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8003008-1. Televisions, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004001-1. Consumer participation, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004002-1. Credit, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004003-0. Life insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004004-1. Beverages, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004005-1. Credit, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004006-1. Credit, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004007-2. Insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004008-2. Insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004009-2. Insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004010-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8004011-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006001-3. Real estate, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006002-1. Telecommunications, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006003-1. Lawn mowers, 1980 (Box 18)
    - 8006004-1. Lawyers, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006005-2. Dairy products, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006006-2. Dairy products, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006007-2. Dairy products, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006008-2. Dairy products, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006009-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006010-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8006011-0. Consumer protection, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8007001-3. Telecommunications, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8007002-1. Credit, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8007003-1. Hazardous products, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8007004-1. OTC (over the counter) drugs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8007005-3. Public utilities, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8007006-1. Moving industry, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8007007-1. Trucking industry, 1980 (Box 18)
    - 8007008-1. Trucking industry, 1980 (Box 18)
    - 8007009-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8007010-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8008001-1. Insulation, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8008002-2. Housing, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8008003-3. Dentistry, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8008004-3. Medical care, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8008005-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8008006-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8008007-1. Life insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009001-1. Telecommunications, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009002-1. Standards, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009003-1. Credit, 1980 (Box 18)
    - 8009004-1. Hazardous products, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009005-1. Credit, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009006-1. Lawn mowers, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009007-1. Telecommunications, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009008-1. Lawyers, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009009-1. Funerals, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009010-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009011-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009012-1. Life insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009013-1. Life insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009014-1. Life insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8009015-1. Life insurance, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8010001-1. Housing, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8080002-1. Automobile imports, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8010003-1. Automobile imports, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8010004-3. Funerals, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8010005-1. Used automobiles, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8011001-1. Banks, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012001-1. Moving industry, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012002-1. Credit, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012003-0. Mortgages, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012004-1. Mortgages, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012005-1. Credit, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012006-2. Real estate, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012007-1. Mortgages, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012008-1. Strip mining, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012009-1. Natural gas, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8012010-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
  - 1981, 17
    - 8101001-1. Insulation, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8101002-1. Credit, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8101003-0. School lunch programs, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8102001-1. Manufactured housing, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8102002-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8102003-1. Oil industry, 1981 (Box 18)
    - 8102004-1. Banks, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103001-3. Medical care, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103002-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103003-3. Dentistry, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103004-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103005-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103006-1. Automobile safety restraints, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103007-1. Telecommunications, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103008-1. Oil industry, 1981 (Box 18)
    - 8103009-1. School lunch programs, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103010-3. Medical care, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103011-1. Standards, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103012-3. School lunch programs, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8103013-1. Oil industry, 1981 (Box 18)
    - 8104001-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8104002-1. Insulation, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8104003-1. Mortgages, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8105001-1. Funerals, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8105002-1. Credit, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8105003-1. Regulatory agencies, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8105004-1. Automobile safety restraints, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8105005-1. Regulatory agencies, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8106001-1. Consumer movement, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8106002-3. Public utilities, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8107001-1. Credit, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8107002-4. Consumer protection, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8107003-1. Highway safety, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8107004-2. Oranges, 1981 (Box 18)
    - 8107005-1. Public utilities, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8107006-1. Coal mining, 1981 (Box 18)
    - 8107007-2. Oranges, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8108001-4. Lead-based paint, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8108002-1. Moving industry, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8108003-1. Coal mining, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8109001-1. Lawyers, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8109002-1. Lawyers, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8109003-3. Credit, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8110001-0. Warranties, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8110002-0. Product liability, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8110003-1. Public utilities, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8110004-1. Lawn mowers, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8110005-1. Consumer bankruptcy, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8110006-1. Banks, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8110007-1. Public utilities, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8111001-1. Lawyers, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8111002-1. Beverages, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8111003-1. Automobile bumper standards, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8112001-1. Regulatory agencies, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8112002-2. Lindane, 1981 (Box 18)
    - 8112003-1. Used automobiles, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8112004-1. Credit, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 8112005-0. Regulatory agencies, 1981 (Box 10)
  - 1982, 18
    - 8201001-1. Telecommunications, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8201002-0. Energy policy, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8201003-1. Energy policy, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8203001-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8203002-1. Telecommunications, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8203003-3. Public utilities, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8203004-1. Consumer bankruptcy, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8204001-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8204002-1. Energy conservation, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8205001-0. Poison control, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8206001-0. Returnable containers, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8206002-1. Standards, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8206003-1. Energy conservation, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8207001-1. Funerals, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8207002-1. Airborne lead pollution, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8207003-1. Automobile safety restraints, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8207004-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8208001-1. Lawyers, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8208002-1. Telecommunications, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8208003-2. Credit, 1982 (Box 10)
    - 8209001-1. Telecommunications, 1982 (Box 11)
    - 8209002-0. Gasoline, 1982 (Box 11)
  - 1983, 19
    - 8301001-1. Consumer bankruptcy, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8303001-1. Lawyers, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8303002-1. Lawyers, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8303003-1. Cost accounting, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8303004-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8303005-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8303006-1. Telecommunications, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8304001-1. Insurance, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8304002-1. Usury laws, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8305001-1. Video sales and rental, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8305002-1. Telecommunications, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8306001-1. Telecommunications, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8307001-1. Office equipment, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8307002-1. Telecommunications, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8307003-1. Advertising, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8308001-1. Lawyers, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8309001-1. Office equipment, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8309002-1. Telecommunications, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8309003-1. Hazardous products, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8310001-1. Hazardous products, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8310002-1. Uniform New Payments Code, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8312001-1. Automobile safety restraints, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8312002-3. Telecommunications, 1983 (Box 11)
    - 8312003-0. Public utilities, 1983 (Box 11)
  - 1984, 20
    - 8402001-1. Video sales and rental, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8403001-0. Consumer protection, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8403002-1. Public utilities, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8403003-1. Office equipment, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8403004-1. Office equipment, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8403005-0. Postal rates, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8403007-0. Flammable fabrics, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8403008-1. Product liability, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8403009-1. Hazardous products, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8404001-1. Hazardous products, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8405001-1. Trademarks, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8405002-1. Trademarks, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8405003-1. Product liability, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8406001-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8406002-1. Consumer protection, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8406003-0. Consumer protection, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8406004-1. Office equipment, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8406005-1. Banks, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8406007-1. Banks, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8407001-1. Standards, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8407003-0. Drug exports, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8407004-1. Drug prices, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8407005-1. Product liability, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8408001-1. Used automobiles, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8408002-0. Drug exports, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8408003-1. Banks, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8409001-1. Product liability, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8409002-1. Banks, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8409003-1. Banks, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8410001-1. Cable television, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8411001-1. Telecommunications, 1984 (Box 11)
    - 8412001-2. Dairy products, 1984 (Box 11)
  - 1985, 21
    - 8501001-2. Eye care, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8501002-1. Mortgages, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8502001-1. Food advertising, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8502002-1. Product liability, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8502003-2. Wastewater, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8502004-2. Wastewater, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8503001-2. Insurance, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8503002-1. Product liability, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8504001-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8504002-1. Alcoholic beverages, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8504003-1. Product liability, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8504004-1. Postal rates, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8504005-1. Mortgages, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8504006-1. Banks, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505001-1. Postal rates, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505002-1. Postal rates, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505004-1. Product liability, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505005-1. Product liability, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505006-1. Product liability, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505007-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505008-1. Product liability, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505009-1. Banks, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505010-1. Mortgages, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8505011-1. Automobile safety defects, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8506002-2. Eye care, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8506003-2. Health spas, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8506004-1. Amusement rides, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8506006-1. Banks, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8507001-2. Insurance, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8507002-2. Insurance, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8508001-2. Oil industry, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8508002-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8508003-2. Dairy products, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8508004-2. Mortgages, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8508005-2. Mortgages, 1985 (Box 18)
    - 8509001-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8509002-2. Dairy products, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8509003-1. Banks, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8510001-1. Drug exports, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8510002-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8510003-2. Credit, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8511001-1. Home recording equipment, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8511002-1. Antitrust, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8511003-1. Banks, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8512001-1. Toxic Substances Strategic Committee, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8512002-2. Housing, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8512003-2. Housing, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8512004-2. Housing, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8512005-2. Housing, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8512006-2. Housing, 1985 (Box 11)
    - 8512007-2. Housing, 1985 (Box 11)
  - 1986, 22
    - 8600001-2. Public Scrutiny: A guide to using publicly-disclosed information about money and politics in California, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8601001-3. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8601002-1. Funerals, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8601003-1. Funerals, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8602001-1. Drug exports, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8602002-3. Insurance, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8602003-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8602004-1. Amusement rides, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8602005-1. Credit cards, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8602006-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603001-1. Record keeping, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603002-1. International trade, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603003-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603004-1. Insurance, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603005-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603006-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603007-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603008-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603009-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8603010-1. Health care costs, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8604001-1. Taxes, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8604002-1. Antitrust, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8604003-1. Automobile bumper standards, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8604004-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8604005-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8605001-1. Home recording equipment, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8605002-1. Drug exports, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8605003-1. Drug exports, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8605004-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8605005-1. Health care costs, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8605006-1. Pesticides, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8605007-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8605008-2. Insurance, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8606001-1. Antitrust, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8606002-1. Investments, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8606003-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8606004-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8606005-2. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8606006-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8606007-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607001-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607002-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607003-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607004-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607005-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607006-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607007-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607009-1. Insurance, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607011-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607012-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8607013-1. School lunch programs, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8608001-1. Home recording equipment, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8608002-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609001-1. Minimum wage, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609002-1. International trade, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609003-1. International trade, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609004-1. Alcoholic beverages, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609005-1. Used automobiles, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609006-1. Antitrust, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609008-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609009-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609010-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609011-1. Insurance, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609012-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609013-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609014-1. Telecommunications, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609015-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8609016-1. Mortgages, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610001-1. Home recording equipment, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610002-1. Alcoholic beverages, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610003-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610004-1. Meat industry, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610005-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610006-1. Product liability, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610007-1. Insurance, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610008-1. Insurance, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610009-0. Dichloromethane, 1986 (Box 11)
    - 8610010-1. Medical malpractice, 1986 (Box 12)
    - 8610012-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 12)
    - 8610013-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 12)
    - 8610014-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 12)
    - 8610015-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 12)
    - 8611001-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 12)
    - 8611002-1. Banks, 1986 (Box 12)
    - 8612001-0. Credit cards, 1986 (Box 12)
  - 1987, 23
    - 8700001-0. Escape from the Pesticide Treadmill, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8701001-1. Banks, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8701002-1. Banks, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8701003-1. Insurance, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8701004-1. Insurance, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8701005-1. Banks, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8702001-1. Trademarks, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8702002-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8703001-1. Insurance, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8703002-1. Insurance, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8703004-1. Credit cards, 1987 (Box 18)
    - 8704001-1. Price-fixing, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8705001-1. Product liability, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8705002-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8706001-1. Pesticides, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8707001-1. Insurance, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8707002-1. Insurance, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8707003-1. Product liability, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8707004-1. Pesticides, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8710001-1. Product liability, 1987 (Box 12)
    - 8710002-1. Credit, 1987 (Box 18)
    - 8711001-1. Credit, 1987 (Box 12)
  - 1988, 24
    - 8800001-1. Class actions, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8801001-1. Mortgages, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8802001-1. Credit, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8803001-1. Issues of concern to older Americans, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8803002-2. Insurance, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8804001-1. Dichlorvos (DDVP), 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8806001-1. Automobile rollover standard, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8806002-1. Food safety (pesticides), 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8806003-1. Medical care, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8806004-1. Food safety (pesticides), 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8808001-1. Medical care, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8809001-0. Drinking water, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8810001-0. Drinking water, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8811001-1. Antitrust, 1988 (Box 12)
    - 8812001-1. Banks, 1988 (Box 12)
  - 1989, 25
    - 8900001-2. Regulatory Law Reporter, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8901001-1. Food inspections, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8901002-1. Long Term Care: Analysis of Public Policy Options, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8902001-1. Product liability, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8903001-0. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8903002-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8903003-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8903004-1. Banks, 1989 (Box 18)
    - 8903005-1. Banks, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8903006-1. Insurance, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8905001-1. Insurance, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8905002-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8905003-0. Banks, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8906001-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8907001-1. Insurance, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8907002-1. Tobacco, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8910001-1. Resolution Trust Corporation, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8910002-1. Medical care, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8911001-0. Food safety (pesticides), 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8911002-1. Insurance, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8911003-1. Insurance, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8911005-1. Insurance, 1989 (Box 12)
    - 8912001-1. Resolution Trust Corporation, 1989 (Box 12)
  - 1990, 26
    - 9000001-2. Financial Information Bank for Refugees and Immigrants, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9000002-2. Community Reinvestment: Putting Substance in Your Program, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9000003-0. Biotechnology and Milk, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9001001-1. Resolution Trust Corporation, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9001002-1. Food labeling, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9002001-1. Insurance, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9002002-1. Home equity loans, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9002003-2. Medical care, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9003001-1. Insurance, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9003002-1. Banks, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9003003-2. Mortgages, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9004001-1. Insurance, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9004002-1. Trademarks, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9005001-1. Manufactured housing, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9005002-1. Product liability, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9005003-1. Intellectual property, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9005004-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9005005-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9006001-1. Medical care, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9006002-1. Credit, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9006003-1. Insurance, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9007001-1. Manufactured housing, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9007002-1. Mortgages, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9007003-1. Mortgages, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9009001-1. Lead pollution, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9009002-1. Mortgages, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9009003-1. Insurance, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9010001-1. Automobile insurance, 1990 (Box 12)
    - 9011001-2. Code Blue: The Medi-Cal Emergency (insurance), 1990 (Box 12)
  - 1991, 27
    - 9100001-1. Price-fixing, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9100002-1. Price-fixing, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9100003-2. Credit, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9100004-2. Automobile insurance, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9100005-2. Medical care, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9100006-2. Uniform Commercial Code, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9100007-0. Toxic Chemical Accident Risks in New York City, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9101001-1. Medical care, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9103001-1. Automobile insurance, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9103002-2. The Right Way to Spend California's 70 Billion Health Care Dollars, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9104001-1. Lead poisoning, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9104002-1. Banks, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9104003-1. Banks, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9104004-0. Health care costs, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9104005-1. Banks, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9104006-1. Insurance, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9104007-2. Insurance, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9105001-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9106001-1. Credit, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9106002-1. Health care costs, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9111001-1. Health care costs, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9111002-1. Credit, 1991 (Box 12)
    - 9112001-1. insurance, 1991 (Box 12)
  - 1992, 28
    - 9200001-1. Codex Alimentarius, 1992 (Box 12)
    - 9200002-2. Meeting Statutory Deadlines: Contractual and Financial Injury Litigation, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9201001-1. GATT (General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade), 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9201002-1. GATT (General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade), 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202001-1. Nutrition labeling, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202002-1. Nutrition labeling, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202003-1. Nutrition labeling, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202004-1. Nutrition labeling, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202005-1. Nutrition labeling, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202006-1. Petitions, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202007-1. Nutrition labeling, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202008-1. Nutrition labeling, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202009-1. Nutrition labeling, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202010-1. Food labeling, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9202011-0. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9203001-1. Insurance, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9203002-1. Pesticides, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9203003-1. Insurance, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9204001-1. Infomercials, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9204002-1. Insurance, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9204003-3. Texas Non-Profit Hospitals: Doing Their Fair Share?, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9205001-1. Insurance, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9206001-1. Insurance, 1992 (Box 13)
    - 9206002-1. Product liability, 1992 (Box 13)